How y'all doing? Y'ALL GOOD?
OH, MAN. THANK Y'ALL SO much for coming.
Ah,
you guys
uh
ready to be offended?
No, don't [\h__\h] say that and then go
on Twitter afterwards like, "Oh, Matt
has some opinions of his own." And end
my [\h__\h] career, okay? Just want to
have a good time tonight, all right?
Comedy almost isn't fun, okay? Having to
adhere to everybody's sensitivities.
Since when?
That [\h__\h] is so new. Remember like 3
years ago when no one gave a [\h__\h] about
you felt? Like 3 years ago if you were
in public and were like, "I don't like"
a stranger would come up and be like,
"Shut up, bitch." And punch you in your
chest. Like, "Ah, now I hurt on the
outside and the inside."
I feel like we've gotten so sensitive as
a society, man. We've gotten so soft.
Like fresh out the pool dick soft. That
only fellas understand that. You get out
that cold water, you don't even
recognize yourself and you be like,
"Whose dick is this?
Who put a baby dick on me?"
That's how I feel like we all as a
society, man. Just all soft.
It's exhausting. So, I'm glad we could
all come together for a night of
laughter. It's good to see y'all.
Black people.
Good to see y'all.
White people.
Sitting in the back. How's it feel?
Yeah, you're smiling. Good. I'm glad
you're in a good mood.
Did you say sorry today?
Did you say sorry to a black person
today?
Get your Venmo out right now. Cash app.
Every black person in here $5.
Gets you through the rest of the
We're going to get these reparations one
way or another, okay? I'm sorry it took
so long. I just got here, all right?
Y'all got to learn how to take Bitcoin
or something, but we going to we going
to figure it out.
Ah, white people been so sorry in 2021,
haven't they? Oh my god. It's been my
favorite show to watch.
Just white people trying to out-woke
each other in front of black people.
Cuz it'll always start reasonable and
then just gradually get out of hand.
Like white person number one will start
low.
Like, "Well, you know,
I voted for Obama two times in a row."
You're like, "All right. Solid politics,
okay."
Now white person number two has to top
Obama. So, he's like, "That's crazy. I
was just talking about how Jesus was
black."
You're like, "Yeah, well, walked on
water, probably couldn't swim."
I'll check out. Now white person number
three's got to top Obama and black
Jesus. He's panicking. He says some
ignorant [\h__\h] like, "Well, Madea is my
favorite franchise." YOU'RE LIKE,
"GOTCHA.
LIAR.
Madea is nobody's favorite franchise.
Not even black people's, okay? You're a
reacher. I think it goes Soul Plane than
Madea movies."
God.
Ah, it's all this white guilt.
It's heavy.
Starting to feel like alcoholism a
little bit.
I'm like every room I enter is like a AA
meeting where I got to plead my case.
Like I have to enter every situation
like, "Hey guys, my name is Matt. Just
want to introduce myself. Let you know I
do identify as a straight white male."
And everybody's like, "Boo."
You're like, "Ah, I know. I know I'm
trash, but I would I would really
appreciate it if you use my proper
pronoun, the problem."
What an uncomfortable time
to be a straight white male.
It's a tough time for my people.
For once, you know. It's You got to know
when to fold them. You know what I mean?
We stayed in the game too long with
can't be doing that. Coming back to
haunt us hard.
Rightfully so.
It's just uncomfortable cuz to be a
straight white male in 2021, you're kind
of guilty by association, aren't you?
Which is a shitty place to be if you
didn't do anything.
Like I just turned 25.
I just got here. You know what I mean?
Like I didn't do anything. I'm a new
white. Like give me a chance.
Give me a chance to white my wrongs. You
know what I MEAN?
JUST WANT TO SING ALONG to some songs,
you know what I mean? It's
Just give me a chance. It wasn't It's
not my fault. It's not like I made the
conscious decision to be born a straight
white male.
I probably would have.
Historically speaking, why not be on a
winning team? You know what I mean?
But I didn't get to choose. It wasn't my
decision. Therefore, I can't
I can't apologize for it. That'd be
weird.
And And you don't have to. That's the
thing. You don't have to apologize for
it. Just be a decent [\h__\h] human
being.
Is that too much to ask?
Listen to the sound of white guilt. Ah.
Music to my ears.
Don't have to apologize for it. And I
And I won't.
I'll apologize for being born a straight
white male
when LeBron James apologizes for being
6'9".
Didn't choose this life. Just happened
to be born that way, right? And they
both have their own set of perks, don't
they? Like sure, he can do a [\h__\h]
windmill 360 dunk and I can raise my
voice to the police. So, it's
it's a give and a take, you know what I
mean? Like
I'd love to jam on a [\h__\h] but I
guess I'll just get out of this ticket.
Got to choose your superpower, man. Life
ain't fair for everybody, okay?
Make white people uncomfortable. Check.
Ah, I'm so happy to be shooting this in
LA. I love LA.
AH, I LOVE IT BECAUSE I'M NOT FROM HERE.
SO, I have perspective.
Um I'm actually from Ohio.
Yeah, that's right. That That's That
That felt as welcoming as it should
Man, if you've never been to Ohio, you
you don't got them. You absolutely
don't. I don't care who died there. Send
an email, okay? You do not have to go.
It's so trash. Oh my god. I'm not even
from like a fun part of Ohio. I didn't
get like Cleveland or Cincinnati,
nothing fun. I'm from the middle of
nowhere, like hour west of Columbus,
surrounded by cornfields, country the
sticks we call it. Population like 1,500
people. Like the kind of small town
where like the gas station's also the
grocery store.
You know what I mean? [\h__\h] around and
get some sandwiches and some diesel. You
here? Might as well save a trip.
My hometown was so country, man. We used
to have uh
we used to have drive your tractor to
school day.
Swear to god. Do you guys remember
school spirit week? Well, like every day
of the week would have a theme to it
like pajama day or twin day. We would
have one day in that week when like the
rich kids would pull up and just [\h__\h]
flex on us John Deere style.
And the women in my school would just
get wet. Like, "Oh my lord, he's got
land." Cuz that's all people cared about
where I was from was [\h__\h] farming.
Like you didn't need 8 inches if you had
8 acres. LIKE THAT WAS
THAT WAS THE BIGGEST FLEX YOU COULD come
with. You couldn't compete with a
farmer. If he's plowing land, he could
plow your [\h__\h] Straight up. Like
there's just nothing you could do.
Nothing you could do.
But it's the type of small town where
like
life just kind of dissipates. You know
what I mean? Like everyone lives the
exact same lifetime line.
Like you you you go to high school, you
get pregnant,
then you graduate, maybe. And then you
get a job, get married, and so on and so
forth. Then you die in this hometown.
It's depressing. Nothing to do.
There's nothing to do for fun there.
Everybody just drinks and does drugs.
But not cool like we do it, you know?
Theirs is cuz they're sad.
It's so depressing, man.
I didn't realize drugs were as big of a
problem when I was living there.
But apparently it's gotten worse. Um I
found out about 3 or 4 weeks ago this
kid who I went to school with. He's like
two grades older than me. Didn't know
each other too well. There's only like
300 people in our school, so we kind of
know each other. Found out like 3 or 4
weeks ago this kid um
OD'd from heroin
in this town at at his job. The same job
he got when we were in high school. He
lived and died there.
And obviously the whole town got
together and they mourned the loss of
their dealer.
No, guys, don't get weird, okay? There
was No, there was a silver lining
moment. The whole town, I swear to god,
they started a GoFundMe and they raised
enough money so that they could get him
a memorial bench at his favorite park.
Which I thought was a really sweet
momento, you know, to provide other
people seating
to do their heroin.
I've never done heroin, but I imagine
you want to sit down.
Okay, whatever. You guys don't know him.
Okay, I'm just giving you a little
perspective. That I could have been a
bench, okay? But I'm not.
Nothing like where I'm from. It's so
weird.
I'm good-looking.
I don't like it any more than you guys
do, okay? This is not good for comedy,
okay? And it's so weird for me. My looks
are so confusing to me because you guys
haven't known me my entire life, so you
have no context of this, but
this [\h__\h]
just happened.
Puberty hit me so disrespectfully late.
I was ugly as [\h__\h] for the first 22
years of my life. I was so ugly for so
long. If I would have been on Wayfair,
they would have returned me immediately.
Like I was so ugly.
Don't Oh, okay. I spent the first 22
years of my life building a personality
for what?
You think I need to be funny now? No,
it's a [\h__\h] waste of my time, to be
honest.
It's gotten me nowhere.
Oh, and it's and it's so weird because
when you spend so much of your life as
one thing and then you're drastically
changed into something else overnight,
it [\h__\h] with you
emotionally. Like I still It's still so
new to me that I don't quite
grasp it. It doesn't I don't see myself
that way. Like I know I look like every
fuckboy ever, but I do identify as a
ugly person. So,
I I think that does technically make me
trans.
Um
trans handsome, transome. Uh
You know, we wait till we get our
bathrooms. It's going to be all mirrors,
bunch of pretty people doing cocaine.
It's going to be dope. But y'all can't
come.
It's so weird, man.
It's such a drastic lifestyle change,
too, because
people treat you so differently. Nobody
likes attractive people, right? You
assume their lives are easier. Like
there's no sympathy for pretty people at
all.
Which is another thing you guys might
not know about me is I have clinical
depression and an anxiety disorder.
And
you guys are just waiting for the
punchline. That's how [\h__\h] up it is
that I that I can come up here and vent
to y'all basically being like, "Help."
And y'all are like, "Get your cute ass
out of here."
And it's not funny. Awesome. Okay, it
It's so weird. There's no sympathy for
pretty people. No one gives a [\h__\h] how
sad you are if you have high cheekbones
at all.
People act like I don't have any
problems at all. I could be crying my
eyes out in bed and people are just
like, "Ooh, what could you possibly be
so upset about, huh? I bet you're just
swimming in pussy." And it's like,
"Yeah, but
you know what I'm not swimming in?
Self-confidence, security, believe it or
not, someone who listens to me. I can't
even hang myself cuz my jawline will cut
the [\h__\h] rope."
And I'm just on the ground, handsome.
Even if I did die, it's got to be a open
casket.
People are like, "Goddamn, he looks good
in a suit. That's really nice. That's
Blue is his color. That is nice."
There's no sympathy for pretty people.
You guys are lucky.
Count your blessings, uggos. [\h__\h] ain't
sweet up here, either, okay? Everybody's
dealing with [\h__\h]
I just want you to remember that.
Remember that. Next time you're in bed
having the worst day,
crying your eyes out and your friends
are by your bedside or blowing up your
phone like, "Oh my god, are you okay? Is
there anything we can do to make you
feel better? What's wrong?"
Just remember,
means you're ugly.
Stop I don't make up the rules, okay?
I'm sorry. If you were cute, they'd be
like, "Get up, [\h__\h] We're going to the
club. Free Molly rocks. We'll be right
back to it. No problem." But
rules are rules.
It's weird because it's given me um
it's given me the perspective of
not judging people based on how they
look.
I'm a big fan of that.
That's why I like the masks.
Love it. You don't know who's ugly with
a mask on, do you?
It's kind of a fun game to play, isn't
it? Just walking up through the grocery
store like, "Does this [\h__\h] have a
beak?" Like you don't know.
You don't know what people's situations
are. You got to get to know them before
you can judge. Like you wouldn't be able
to just assume I'm a douchebag if I have
my mask on. You'd have no basis. I could
walk into any Starbucks with my mask on.
They would just think I'm any random
lesbian. You know what I mean? I could
be anybody.
Could be anybody. Go in like, "What's
your name?" I'm like, "Matt." They're
like, "You are so brave."
And the code to your bathroom is 47.
Man, the masks made it so hard to holler
at people, didn't it? Cuz you don't know
what 60% of their face looks like. That
[\h__\h] was so dangerous.
You ever talk to somebody for a while
and you're like, "I I got to know." You
got to come up with some like cute,
clever way to get them to pull their
mask down. Say some dumb [\h__\h] like,
"Have you smiled today? Have you
You smile You look You I feel like you
have a cute smile. Would you give me a
smile real quick?" And you've been
chatting forever and she's been all eyes
and she's like, "I don't know. I guess I
could give you A LITTLE
GOD DAMN IT! OH MY GOD, I TALKED TO YOU
FOR AN HOUR.
Gave you my time.
I had no idea.
But I like it. I'm a big fan of not
judging people based on how they look.
Cuz if there's one thing we all have in
common, every single person in this
room,
is everybody's going through something.
Right? Everybody in here is dealing with
some [\h__\h] that nobody else has any idea
about.
I go through [\h__\h] all the time. You guys
have no clue.
Like one thing you might not know is uh
I have terrible luck.
Bad random [\h__\h] happens to me all the
time.
And uh I'll tell you an incredibly
embarrassing and humbling story.
Need a moment.
Just thirsty.
Uh
last year
I had to have surgery
on my nipples.
They're fine now.
You can stop looking.
Last year I ended up developing this
freak medical condition. Like this [\h__\h]
is so rare, it only happens to like
12-year-old boys and 80-year-old men and
somehow I'm both. Like it's so rare. My
doctor looked me in my eyes and was
like,
"I don't know why this happened to you."
I was like, "First of all, I'm up here.
Second,
don't not give me an answer, okay? It's
not very professional."
It was this freak condition that was
causing the breast tissue um the breast
tissue under my pecs that
bench about 285, 8 to 10 reps.
That's neither here nor there. Uh it was
causing the breast tissue to grow
incongruently under my nipples. Now,
before your imagination start running
[\h__\h] wild, let me shut that down
right now, okay? Whatever image you're
drawing up in your head, get it out of
there. It wasn't anything drastic at
all. If you had never seen me shirtless
before, you would never even know the
difference. But you know your body,
right? If something's off just the
littlest bit, you notice it more than
anybody else ever would. So, it was it
was just messing with me mentally. Like
I wasn't I wasn't comfortable in my own
skin. I wasn't comfortable taking my
shirt off. My Instagram was suffering.
I was like,
"You know, this this is messing with
business. You got to get checked out."
So, I go to the doctor
and he's like,
"Yeah, you got it." I'm like,
"Up."
I said, "What What do we What do we do?"
And he explains to me it's actually an
irreversible condition, meaning it'll
never just go away. You can't take
medicine for it. You You have to have it
surgically removed from your body.
I was like, "All right, man. What's
What's the damage on something like
that?" And he explains to me that this
surgery is going to be $9,000.
Nine racks. Out of pocket, mind you, cuz
technically it's cosmetic. It's not
life-threatening. So, insurance doesn't
cover it.
$9,000 in the middle of the pandemic,
which I don't know how much you guys
know about stand-up comedy, but
this is the first time I've been inside
in like 2 years, man. I've been
performing in pickup trucks and Kmart
parking lots. Money has not been good to
me. I definitely didn't have $9,000 to
drop on something that wasn't going to
kill me.
Breast implants are $10,000.
So, if you think my life is just oh so
easy and I have no problems at all, you
go home
and you think about the dilemma that I
had to sit with by myself every night
leading up to this like, "God damn.
Am I about to drop nine
thousand dollars on something that's
ultimately cosmetic and really only
affects how I feel about myself and
whoever it is that I'm intimate with.
Do I drop $10,000?
Get these titties and clean up at the
women's Olympics. Are you kidding me?
If I go full transition, it is over for
you [\h__\h]
I don't even run track and field. I'm
placing bronze, guaranteed, okay?
I'm a decent looking dude, but I'm a bad
[\h__\h] straight up.
Ah.
Didn't need to tell y'all that.
I don't have a sponsorship.
Somebody going to buy this a White Claw
and be like, "Yeah, 60 grand."
I'm going to be like, "It's all here,
bro. I don't know."
No, you got nothing. I'll let you suck
one for 30 seconds. That's
All right, that weird. Um
When I got this chin,
I thought things would be different.
I thought things would be easier.
Thought dating would be easier.
No.
Maybe it's me. I'm I'm very picky. I'm
so hard to date. I I have such a
specific type.
I I predominantly only date older women.
Just personal preference.
Like late 30s, early 40s is Oh my god,
such a sweet spot. Oh.
Well, not ones who sit in the back.
This [\h__\h] is wooing from her handicap
spot in the parking lot.
I also don't know if you match the
criteria. It's got to be late 30s, early
40s, man.
Cuz women are kind of like Captain
Crunch, right?
Like they're the best right before
they're gross.
[\h__\h] y'all, that's a solid cereal joke,
okay?
Cuz
Cuz if you [\h__\h] WITH CAPTAIN CRUNCH,
IF YOU [\h__\h] WITH CAPTAIN CRUNCH, YOU
KNOW THERE'S A very fine window. If it
tears your mouth up and it's oatmeal,
okay? It's a very fine line. It's like
42. Apparently, who knew?
Some of y'all not laughing cuz you
sitting there with some grits. And
that's fine. That's
Snitch on yourself if you want to.
Maybe a little brown sugar in the front
row.
Put your dash on.
That's how you holler.
No verbal communication needed. I knew
what that meant.
Yeah, older women are so dope, man.
Sometimes they got kids,
which means they got snacks.
I'm so easy, man. I can't cook at all.
I'll [\h__\h] you for a Lunchable. That's a
fact. I'm so easy. Are you kidding me?
If you have a Crock-Pot, I will shut
[\h__\h] down.
To the best of my ability. I don't know.
I don't know who you were dating before
me or what they were doing, but I don't
want to make
false promises.
Cuz sex is hard.
It is.
Ladies, y'all have it so easy.
Oh, never heard that before?
I fully believe I fully believe women
have sex so much easier than men.
Oh, yeah.
One hoe in the back just like, "Yeah, it
just opens up. It's crazy. It just does
its own thing."
Dude
Dudes come out of her [\h__\h] like this.
I think it's so true. It's so much less
work.
All you technically have to do is like
You know what I mean? Like
That's all you Just be punctual. That's
your only responsibility is to be on
time cuz we will start without you.
That's the only requirement.
Do you real-
Do you realize as a man, like there's a
certain level of excitement I have to
get and I have to maintain this
excitement the entire time while I'm
focusing on a million things. I'm
focusing on me. I'm focusing on you. I'm
switching positions. It's a full court
press the entire time. You focus so much
that sometimes sometimes you go quick.
You [\h__\h] leave me hanging ON THIS
RIGHT NOW? LIKE I'm the only dude who's
at AT MY SPECIAL. Y'ALL GOING TO
DISRESPECT ME LIKE THIS?
Y'all ain't [\h__\h] man. Oh, oh, I'm the
only person ever to bust fast.
Hilarious, you guys.
Y'all ain't [\h__\h] You know that?
It happens to the best of us, okay?
There's no reason to be a big deal,
be a big problem about it.
Would you be mad if your food came out
early at a restaurant?
No. You'd be like, "The chef is killing
it. I got all this time for activities."
I don't come fast. I just respect your
schedule, okay? I know
I know you got to take your kids to
school in the morning, so.
Sex is hard. The build-up is fun,
though.
Like sexting. Sexting is the most fun.
Oh my god.
Dudes love sexting.
We're so good at it.
Cuz we're just lying the whole time. Oh,
it's so easy. We lie so much. We talk so
much game of what we can't wait to do to
y'all when we see it. We ain't doing
none of that ever at all.
We're like the J.K. Rowling of dick
pics. Like we're just writing fairy
tales. It's [\h__\h] we are never going to
do to y'all ever. We set the bar too
high. We say crazy stuff like like,
"Girl, when I see you, I'm going to I'm
going to put you up against the wall.
I'm going to I'm going to [\h__\h] you in
the curtains." Like you ain't [\h__\h]
nobody in the curtains.
You've been to my house. I got blinds.
You want me to scratch my back up?
Not very practical.
I lied recently.
It's how the game goes.
I was sexting with this girl and like
I could see where she was going with it,
but like it was just rude of her to
assume.
Like I was sexting with this girl. She
was like,
"I'm only 103 lbs. You could throw me
around."
Like I responded as a dude. I was like,
"That's right."
But on the inside, I was like, "That's
more than you think it is. That's
Fellas, BACK ME UP on this. But 103? Get
the [\h__\h] out. Oh, it's nothing? It's
It's light work? Oh, pick me up then.
How about How about [\h__\h] your lower
back? How about that?
I haven't done a deadlift since 10th
grade. Now [\h__\h] you's got to be leg
day.
Now I got to [\h__\h] you with one of those
weight trainer belts the Mexicans wear
in the gym for no reason.
Mexicans be in the gym doing all arms.
Got a whole back brace.
Like why you got jeans on?
You said some people didn't like that?
Well, it is what it is.
I know. I talk a lot of [\h__\h] but I'm
the problem.
I'm I'm I'm well aware.
I'm so I'm so picky.
I have a lot of red flags that I look
for.
That's why like the first date's always
the hardest cuz you're you look like
you're looking for things to not like.
And that's so tough cuz there's
a lot of [\h__\h] I don't like.
I'll list a couple of red flags for you.
Feel free to tell me if I'm out of
pocket for not being okay with some of
these things. Um
Red flag number one.
I don't [\h__\h] with girls who go on boats.
It's hoe [\h__\h]
Feel like a lot of people in here have
been cheated on.
Not on land. That's what I feel.
Yeah, but I'm happy to have y'all
support. It's cuz it's insanity to me.
If you live in LA and you date a hot
girl for long enough, at some point this
chick will come to you and say something
like, "Babe, there's just this guy, a
friend of mine, who
who wants to just take me and my eight
hot girlfriends into the abyss." Are you
out of your [\h__\h] mind?
Why?
What? Stay dry. What?
Like no.
People get [\h__\h] on boats.
Boats were built for [\h__\h]
Since the beginning of boats, people
been [\h__\h] on them. B O A T. Bring out
ass and titties. It's been in front of
us
the whole time.
It's always been an acronym.
My girl not getting on no boats.
No kayaks.
No canoes.
No No No paddle boats. You know, I'm
working up a sweat next to another man.
Not dealing with it. That's why women
love Titanic so much.
Because it's a beautiful story about a
chick who cheats on her man with a scrub
while her boyfriend IS ON THE SHIP.
NO.
YOU SAY YOU LIKE BOATS? Get out. Get out
right now. You got big boat energy right
now and I'm not [\h__\h] with it.
So that's the big one.
Um
Red flag number two.
I don't [\h__\h] with Ouija boards.
Obviously, this only pertains to white
women. Um
And you know what? This shouldn't even
be a story that I have to tell, but it's
been weighing heavy on my soul lately,
so I'll I'll let y'all in.
A couple of years ago, I was doing a
show at a comedy club in Hollywood and I
get off stage and this beautiful girl
comes up to me, gives me her number.
This happens all the time.
I'm
kidding. Um She comes up to me, gives me
her number. She's beautiful. We go our
separate ways for the evening. The very
next day, she texts me and was like,
"Hey, I want to come over." And I'm
like, "Bet. Still got it." You know what
I mean?
So, she comes over. I let her in. We go
sit on the couch. And it's me and her on
the couch, and then my roommate is down
the hall in his room. His door is open.
You can't see into the living room from
his room, but he hears all of this. He's
witness. So, we sit on the couch, and
for the first 2 minutes, I'm asking all
the questions that guys, you know,
don't care about. Um but you don't want
to We don't want to come across as too
eager, so we ask silly questions like,
you know, you got a
family or,
you know, those your real ears? You
didn't get your ears done? Like [\h__\h]
vague [\h__\h] that we don't really care
about at all.
So, we're talking for like 2 minutes,
and then she hits me with,
"Yeah, um
do you have a Ouija board?"
And I'm like,
"I don't
even have a headboard.
Nah, don't Don't got that on me. Sorry."
And she goes, "Well, can we go to Target
and get one?"
I'm like,
"No.
I've got Disney Plus.
That's what we're doing."
And she's not giving up. She was like,
"Wha- Well, can I make one?" I'm like,
"What in the demonic charcuterie
are you trying to bring into my home
right now?"
And
I'm trying to hit.
So,
I'm like, "Yeah, sure. If you can find
the things in my apartment to make a
Ouija board, go ahead." Biggest mistake
of my life.
This stranger who I just met starts
ransacking my apartment. She's opening
every cabinet, every cupboard, every
closet, going through everything. I
don't know if you guys have ever seen a
video of when a deer accidentally gets
inside,
and it starts hitting everything like
it's never seen walls before?
But she's going crazy. She finds a
couple of markers to write stuff down.
She finds this little glass piece to be
like the centerpiece. And she's like,
That's how hard she's working. She's out
of breath. She's like,
"We don't have something to make the
board." And I was like, "Damn."
Guess we got to watch Monsters Inc. Man.
And she just sit on down. And she goes,
"Hold on a second."
So, she gets up, and she goes over to
the front door. She opens the front
door, and she goes outside. And my
roommate comes down the hallway and is
like,
And I'm like,
So, he goes over and slams the door shut
behind her. I laughed so hard, but
again, there's a mission at hand.
So, I'm like, "All right, stop playing."
So, I get up, I go open the door. It's
been 4 seconds. I go, I open the door.
There's nobody out there. She's gone.
So, I'm like,
"Hey!
Ashley!
I'm going to shut the door.
And once it's shut, it's going to stay
shut. You're going to be stuck out here.
I'm serious, AMANDA.
ALL RIGHT." SO, I GO, I swing the door
and turn around, and straight out of a
scary movie, this chick's foot, bam,
stops it right before it closes on the
frame. I WAS LIKE, "JESUS CHRIST!"
And here comes this chick lugging in
this giant piece of cardboard. I'm like,
"Where did you get that?" She goes, "It
was just out there." [\h__\h] no it
wasn't. No, it was not just out there.
So, she brings it in.
She sets it on the coffee table.
And we both sit on the couch, and I'm I
don't know where it came from. I got to
I I I lift it up. It's from the TV box I
threw in the dumpster 4 days prior.
This chick brought garbage
back into my home to summon the devil.
So, you know the sex is going to be
dope.
She's [\h__\h] crazy. I'm in. I GOT TO DO
IT. You know what I mean?
I mean, I've never smashed a homeless
chick before, but she clearly brought
all of her things.
She's like, "All right, you ready to
make one?" And I'm like,
"I guess. Yeah."
So, she draws it out. And but before I
continue, does anybody not know what a
Ouija board is?
Yeah. Really?
Yeah. You really don't know? I've never
played it. Oh, man. Okay. Well, first of
all, God bless you.
You're so naive. Um
A Ouija board is essentially it's it's a
it's a toy board that you can get from
any store like Walmart or Target or
whatever. It's uh
And people use it to drunk text the
dead, essentially.
It's all it's good for. And it's very
simple layout. Uh it has the the
alphabet right here close center middle
of the boards. It's where um the
centerpiece is supposed to be guided by
a spirit to spell out certain words to
answers that you ask. It's So, the
middle is the alphabet. Right corner is
no.
Left corner is yes.
Alphabet, left yes, no. Yes, alphabet,
no.
So, she draws the whole thing up.
And she's like, "All right. So, there's
a couple of rules you have to know when
you're going to play with a Ouija
board." I was like, "Yeah, duh. I mean,
everybody knows that.
But uh refresh me again."
She was like, "All right, rule number
one,
you never play with it by yourself.
Ever."
I'm like, "Okay."
"Rule number two, you have to remember
to say goodbye." Cuz apparently, you
can't ghost the ghosts.
So, she's like, "All right, let's play."
Okay. So, got our hands on the piece.
And
she's like, "All right, we got to ask it
a question." I go, "Ahead." She's like,
"All right. Um
Okay.
Is there anybody here with us?" And you
just hear my roommate down the hallway
go, "Yeah, his name is Brandon, and he
[\h__\h] lives here."
I was like, "Touché. He pays rent. Um
which do you No."
So,
she's like, "All right, I'll ask it
another question."
"Did anybody die here?"
Doesn't move. I'm like,
"This is crazy."
She's like, "Well, then you ask it
something." I'm like,
"Okay. Um
Should we go lay down in my room?"
OH! OH!
OH!
WE DON'T WANT TO PISS OFF THE DEAD, do
we?
She's like, "You're right." So, we go
lay down.
This chick brings the cardboard in the
room with her. She sets it at the foot
of the bed like it's a golden retriever.
Now, we're under the covers.
We're doing more
makeshift conversation. You know, I'm
like, "You know, you got
dreams or
you know, what's your favorite picture?
You know, just vague [\h__\h] I don't care
about." And about like 4 or 5 minutes
after this,
she just knocks out.
Like not a subtle like, "Mhm, starting
to feel a little bit tired." Like just
straight Yeah, and then I
Like she is slumped.
And now it's her asleep, me under the
covers, and I'm staring down just
terrified of this Samsung TV box.
And all I can think is,
"This [\h__\h] didn't say goodbye."
Now, I'm terrified up by myself. I'm
trying to wake her up. I'm like, "Hey.
HEY.
ALLISON.
GREAT.
She's asleep.
Now, I got to play with it by myself.
Ah.
So, I start jerking off, and she wakes
up straight out of an exorcism, and was
like,
"WHAT ARE YOU DOING?" AND I WAS LIKE,
"OH GOD!" AND I SWEAR TO GOD, A spirit
left my body and hit her right in the
face. It was the craziest thing
I've ever seen.
Oh God.
Uh I never saw her again. I never saw
I'm To this day, I'm not convinced she
wasn't a ghost.
Wouldn't surprise me.
Ah.
That's That's why I can't mess with
young people. I really can't. She was
25, 26. Just put off of it.
Makes me feel so much older dealing with
somebody like that.
I do feel older. I date older women. All
my friends are older.
I [\h__\h] hate kids so much. Kids
[\h__\h] suck, man. Oh my god. They're so
garbage.
I don't like young people at all, man.
We just don't click. I'm not on
I'm on none of the apps that they're on.
What's the What's the one app that
literally every kid is on it? Um
No. Amber Alert?
Every kid is on Amber Alert, aren't
they? It's like maybe they're looking
for you. How many followers you got?
Enough for a search party, I hope.
See, this is hilarious to me cuz I can
feel the hypocrisy radiating off y'all
right now. Like I'm the [\h__\h] That's
adorable. Okay. When's the last time you
got an Amber Alert on your phone and
your first reaction wasn't, "Oh, [\h__\h]
How do I turn this off? How do I
How do I
None of y'all are like, "WE GOT TO FIND
THESE KIDS." NOT ONE PERSON. Y'all
haven't found a kid since milk was in a
carton, okay? Judge me.
It's a terrible app. It's the worst app.
It's vague.
Like, "Be on the lookout for a 2015
silver Prius." Like, is he in my Uber?
Is this a rideshare?
Did I hit pool?
The alarm's the worst part, by far. They
haven't changed the alarm in like 30
years. It's still the same
I get so mad when that [\h__\h] goes off on
my phone. I could be standing next to
the kidnapper. I'd be like, "Hey.
Is it in the settings? Like, I go to
general?
Notification?
I close that with the Wayfair app.
Do you guys remember that?
Do you guys remember when Wayfair was
selling other stuff?
For any of you guys who might not
remember, Wayfair, the uh furniture
company, in 2020 was accused of
allegedly
being involved in human trafficking.
And
we forgave them pretty quick, didn't we?
They're They're killing it. Their
business is booming right now. Supply
the chairs y'all sitting on right now.
So, if you could, please give a warm
round of applause for our sponsor.
Bro, they came back hot with some deals,
too. They were like, "I'm sorry, five.
Our bad, 10."
I was like, "These are the ages of the
discounts." Like, I just don't trust you
anymore.
I don't trust you.
It was bad, man.
We found out as a people, we hate human
trafficking.
But not as much as we hate an
unfurnished patio. Am I right?
Them umbrellas ain't cheap, man.
No, it's not funny. It's not funny. It's
very serious, and I do feel very bad for
all the families affected by that,
obviously. Feel terrible about it. But
I especially feel bad for
the dude who just wanted a desk. You
know what I mean?
How many times have you got the wrong
order in the mail? And I
Now you got to get a crib, too. A lot of
money out of pocket.
It's messed up, man. Can't support them.
Don't Don't support Wayfair.
They're terrible.
Not as bad as IKEA.
But
[\h__\h] IKEA. You kidding me?
They're way worse. IKEA needs to come
with a kid just to help put that [\h__\h]
together. They
Somebody got to hold these sides, bro.
God damn.
Can I go home now? I don't know, man.
That's a lot of leftover pieces. You
sure you didn't skip any steps?
There's always so many leftover pieces
after an IKEA project, isn't there? You
look at a final IKEA piece like,
I guess that's it.
And you find out you messed up on step
eight of 49, you're like,
I guess we just don't have a bottom
shelf. It is what it is.
We'll put tall stuff there.
Guys,
relax.
Still me. Remember the dude who's been
telling jokes for 45 minutes?
Still just a joke. This This is why
comedy is the most frustrating job in
the world. It's because this is the only
job in the world that I would have to
reiterate to y'all what I'm doing, that
I'm just kidding. I don't mean this [\h__\h]
that comes out of my mouth. Rappers
don't have to do that.
Rappers are literally like, "I [\h__\h]
your [\h__\h] and killed your family." And
y'all ARE JUST LIKE,
THEY DON'T GOT TO BE LIKE, "I'M JUST
RAPPING. I'M JUST RAPPING, Y'ALL. I
would
I wouldn't do nothing like that. I'm
David. You know me. I wouldn't do
nothing like that."
So hypocritical, man.
That's the one thing comedians do have
over rappers. It's freedom of speech.
It's kind of like an unwritten rule in
comedy, right? Like, you can joke about
messed up stuff as long as it's funnier
than it is messed up.
And rappers don't get that kind of
leeway. That's not fair. Like, if they
admit to a crime they did on beat, they
still go to jail.
I don't think that's fair. Respect the
artistry. Give them a chance, okay? I
think if you can make a doper song than
the charges you're trying to beat, you
get to go home. I think that's fair.
I think that's fair. All spectrums of
crime, too. Can you imagine Ted Bundy
in court? And they're like, "You're
going to jail forever." And he's like,
"Well, wait till you hear this [\h__\h]
It's a little song I call I eat the
[\h__\h] up, starring J Doms."
Cuz he's a cannibal.
Okay.
That one was a tough sell. That's fine.
I understand. See if we can get y'all
back with something a little bit more
level-headed we can all kind of get on
board with.
Um
gun control?
Why not, right?
Can't be worse than the Wayfair [\h__\h]
It is. This is way worse. If that If
that one wasn't your [\h__\h] buckle up.
Uh this This is a lot harder one to
tackle.
Gun control is so tricky because I
I see both sides.
I do understand. I I I understand the
amendment, everyone's right to have a
gun. That makes sense to me, especially
when it comes to things like protection
or or providing for your family. That
makes sense.
But at the same time,
everybody
Every Not everybody gets a gun, right?
That's crazy. You all know somebody that
you're like, "This [\h__\h] should
not have a gun, right?" It's so easy to
be irresponsible with a gun. When's the
last time you held a gun and didn't DO
THIS [\h__\h]
PEOPLE FREAK OUT EVERY TIME. THEY'RE
LIKE, "NO, DON'T." YOU'RE LIKE, "I
WOULDN'T, but would I?" It's a timeless
bit. That [\h__\h] has been funny for
centuries.
I think it's so easy to be irresponsible
with the gun that I think
a simple interim solution would be it
just needs to be a little bit harder to
get the gun.
That's all I suggest. I think there's so
many tiers to responsibility you should
have to surpass before you can have a
gun. That's all I suggest. And I'm not
even proposing anything difficult.
Simple [\h__\h] like,
if you haven't had sex yet,
straight up, no gun. Okay?
That is way too much power for you. How
you going to pull a trigger before
you've had to pull out? Like, that takes
discipline, and I need to see you in a
moment of crisis, okay? Can you handle
the power?
Do you realize if something as simple as
that was implemented? If something as
simple as having sex was a requirement
for getting a registered firearm, what
kind of impact that would have on the
entire problem?
School shootings would drop off almost
completely.
Have you ever seen pictures of these
kids who shoot up schools?
They are so [\h__\h] ugly. You kind of
get it a little bit. Like, they weren't
[\h__\h] There has never been a handsome
school shooter that they were like, "Ah,
he was GOING TO BE PROM KING." LIKE,
never once.
Never. No one has time to write a
manifesto and get [\h__\h] That's science,
okay?
It's too much detail.
Look, I I'm well aware that school
shootings is a very hard thing to try to
make funny.
But we're going to try.
And I feel like I owe the explanation as
like why Why would I joke about
something this [\h__\h] up? And the reason
being
is it's sort of my coping mechanism. I I
try to make light of terrible
situations, luckily through humor, so
that I'm not sad every [\h__\h] day.
Cuz what's the first thing you do when
you wake up every morning?
Check your phone, right? Probably get on
Twitter or some some sort of news. Yeah,
you get caught up. Doesn't it feel like
there's something negative immediately?
There's so much negativity in front of
our faces daily that I can't imagine
living any kind of life where I don't
have an outlet for that negativity. It
just festers inside of me and makes me a
miserable human being. If I have an
outlet through humor, I'm going to use
it. You be miserable. Not me.
Now, I respect that that's not for
everybody. That's not how everybody's
brain works. Like, I had a woman furious
one time. She stood up in the middle of
a show one time when I was doing some
other school shooting material.
And
she was furious. She stood up and was
like,
"You shouldn't do jokes about school
shootings."
And I was like,
"Why?"
She was like, "Because what if it
happened to you? Hm? What if you lost
your kid in a school shooting incident?
Hm? Could you make jokes about it then?"
And I was like,
"This bitch."
Cuz like, context. Do you know what I
mean? It's a comedy show. Clearly,
everything I'm saying is hypothetical.
Like, I'm not talking about this in a
literal sense, especially cuz I don't
have any [\h__\h] kids, okay? So, it's
not something I have to think about on a
daily basis. But it's something I I
never taken into consideration. So, it
did [\h__\h] me up a little bit. I had to
take a step back as a man and as a
comedian and actually ask myself,
like if
if I lost my kid
in a school shooting incident,
could I ever make jokes about it?
And
the answer's yeah. It's a hard yes for
me, okay? that that is for sure how I
would heal through that traumatic
experience. Are you kidding me? Second
of all, it's my kid. That's [\h__\h] fair
game, okay?
There is no way I'm not killing it at
funeral. Like
he was never good at hide and seek. Like
come on, man. That [\h__\h] is too easy,
bro.
The kids don't play the games anymore.
It's easier targets.
#bringbackhideandseek
I like this topic only because it's it
creates such a divide racially between
black people and white people when it
comes to the topic of school shootings
because
it's it's usually us.
And black people love to joke all the
time. They love to be like, "Oh, you
know, it's all the white kids shooting
up all the schools. Shooting up the
schools is a white kids sport."
I hear that joke all the time. "Shooting
up the schools is a white kids sport."
It's funny. It's it's a good joke.
Until you think about the history of
sports.
Because if I know anything about the
history of sports, it's that
if white people are good at it now,
black people are going to be way better
at it sometime.
Somebody got to be Wilt. Somebody got to
come in and change the game.
Some of you aren't laughing cuz it's
[\h__\h] up and some of you are cuz you're
like,
"He's right."
They're going to be faster. They're
going to be stronger.
And canceled.
Awesome.
Oh, cancel culture.
We got to chill out
with the cancel culture stuff. We got to
chill
out. The spectrum's too broad.
I don't have time to care about
everything because you make such a big
deal about nothing that it takes all of
my attention away from the stuff we
actually should be canceling and
actually should be upset about.
It's so frustrating. Like just pick and
choose, man.
And stop digging up people's old tweets
and [\h__\h]
Straight up. I think it's the most [\h__\h]
made thing you can possibly do.
Because I'm a big believer that
as times change, people change.
A lot of the time for the better. Not
always, obviously there's exceptions,
but a lot of the times. Like there's so
many examples of it in American history
in and of itself. You can look at
someone like
Malcolm X.
Malcolm X spent 10 years in prison for
robbery and arson. Got out, went on to
become a civil rights activist that
literally changed the [\h__\h] world.
Maya Angelou
used to be a prostitute. Went on to be
[\h__\h] is so funny about that?
What white [\h__\h] in the back
laughing at what I read IN FEBRUARY,
HUH?
HE LAUGHED LIKE HE HIT. LIKE YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN? God damn.
She was a prostitute. She went on to
become a poet, an author, another civil
rights activist that again changed the
[\h__\h] world.
Chance the Rapper
used to make good music.
As times change, people change, right?
Not always for the better. I miss Acid
Rap. That's all I'm saying.
Um
and the reason I wanted to talk about
this is because
it happened to me.
A few years ago, um somebody who didn't
like me went online and they dug up a
bunch of tweets of mine from when I was
15 years old. And when I was 15 years
old, uh as I mentioned, I was born and
raised in the middle of [\h__\h] nowhere,
Ohio. Like I didn't know [\h__\h] about
[\h__\h] I couldn't have been more
ignorant. And anybody who says they
didn't do or say some [\h__\h] when they
were 15 years old that they shouldn't
have done or don't regret is a liar.
Okay, that's the time in your life
you're supposed to make mistakes so you
learn from them, you grow from them, you
don't go on to make those same mistakes
when you're a responsible adult, yeah?
So when I was 15 years old, I was going
back and forth on Twitter with my best
friend, Brendan. Now, Brendan and I have
been best friends since preschool, since
4 years old. He's my next door neighbor.
And Brendan also happened to be black.
So Brendan and I were going back and
forth on Twitter one day. And this is
when Twitter was like the group chat.
You know what I mean? You were just
saying crazy [\h__\h] in there cuz it was
just y'all. You didn't think anybody's
going to care 8 years later. So we were
going back and forth on Twitter just
roasting each other, right? He would say
some, I would say some. He would say
some, I would say some. And then he said
some [\h__\h] that really had me [\h__\h] up
because when I when I was 15, I also had
Ohio teeth.
Like I had a big gap in the middle. I
had little gaps on the side. My teeth
were [\h__\h] up. And Brendan said some
[\h__\h] like, "You're the only person I
know who can eat food without opening
their mouth."
And 15-year-old me was shook. I was
like, "God damn, that's you know, that's
a finisher right there."
So the roast battle was clearly over, so
I conceded and I had responded back with
a very famous Chief Keef lyric at the
time from the song "Don't Like". So the
conversation went, "You're the only
person I know who can eat food without
opening their mouth." And I responded,
"Fuck mm that's that [\h__\h] I don't like."
Now, if you're familiar with the song,
you would know I had tweeted the N-word
in the song lyrics to my friend.
And this was incredibly wrong. This was
ignorant, naive, and
stupid. I I wish I had never done it.
And when this resurfaced, people lost
their [\h__\h] mind. I'm sorry.
White people lost their [\h__\h] mind.
They couldn't believe it. They thought I
had just gotten away with being racist
for 8 years. They were like, "What? You
can't say that. You're not black. You're
not in the car by yourself."
Like they thought I had just found a
loophole in racism and squeaked through
the cracks. And black people couldn't
believe that I knew who Chief Keef was.
That was the biggest uproar amongst the
black community. They were like, "He
[\h__\h] with Sosa? I HAD NO IDEA."
IT WAS INSTANT OUTRAGE amongst the
whites, okay?
And
this was such an uncomfortable situation
because white people love to be offended
for other people.
It's our favorite extracurricular
activity to be like, "Ooh, ooh, did you
Did you Did you see?"
And what you be upset about stuff you
didn't you weren't even initial
initially upset about. White people are
like PC gladiators. JUST, "ARE YOU NOT
OUTRAGED?"
I WASN'T.
Now I am.
And again, this was a very tough
position to be put in because
white people have ruined every excuse in
the book to get out of being called
racist.
They ruined all of them. And
fortunately, but unfortunately,
I fit a massive cliché.
If you or anybody watching were to take
the slightest glimpse into my life, you
wouldn't have to look far at all.
You would see that
all
of my friends are black.
All of them. That's one. There's
There's others, I swear.
All of them are black. I have one white
friend and he's Russian. His name is
Vladislav. And I don't
I don't know how much y'all know about
Russians, but they're the black people
of white people, okay? They're so dope.
So
to my naivety, I'm trying to state my
case to these strangers online who don't
know who I am or know anything about me
cuz from my perspective, I'm like, "No,
like what what are you talking about?
I'm
I'm not racist. If you look at the
people who I hold closest in my life,
the people who mean more to me than my
actual blood family, the people I love
most, who I would probably [\h__\h] die
for, you would see that they're black."
Like what I did was obviously stupid and
wrong, but I didn't mean anything
malicious by it. I would never in my
[\h__\h] life mean anybody any hate or
harm based on the color of their skin.
That's outrageous to me. And the most
frustrating thing about the entire
experience and arguing with these people
online was that
there's still people who don't believe
me.
There's people right now, I'm sure,
watching me online this is just another
white dude trying to get out of another
sticky situation.
And I understand that.
But at the same time,
I also don't have to convince you of a
single [\h__\h] thing.
I
I know who I am. I know I'm not racist.
I know how many times I've jacked off to
Queen Latifah's Beauty Shop.
Y'all sleeping? Oh, y'all sleeping, man.
That [\h__\h] is a classic. They're so
goddamn fine in that movie. Oh.
Woo.
So
this is when the conversation got really
interesting because the problem shifted
subjects. The issue started with a
stupid mistake I made when I was 15
years old and it shifted to white people
now being uncomfortable with my
comfortability with black people. Like
they were they were very uncomfortable
with it. They were saying outrageous
[\h__\h] They would be like,
"Oh, I bet you hang out with so many
black people so that you can justify
saying racist [\h__\h] like that."
For real?
That's how you think racism and
discrimination works?
All right, bet. So, if I hate gay
people, I'm out here sucking so much
dick
just so I can be like, "Ugh, these homos
are disgusting. Am I right?
Oh my god.
That's not how racism and discrimination
works."
I wouldn't put myself in that situation.
But, they kept going. They got more and
more ignorant. They're like, "Oh,
why do you hang out with so many black
people then, huh? What do you want to be
black?" [\h__\h]
a little bit. A little bit.
It's so much cooler some of the time,
okay?
Every white person wishes they were
black a little bit. Any white person who
says they don't is a [\h__\h] liar or a
cop, okay? Do not believe that
for even a second, okay?
But, the silver lining of all of this is
it made me do so much reflecting. Like,
things that I I never had to put any
thought into because they were such
first nature to me, I actually
thought about.
Like, I had never thought about why
all of my friends are black. I had never
thought about why I'm so comfortable
with black people or why I appreciate
black people so much.
So, I did a lot of self-reflecting on it
and the conclusion I came to
is
that
nobody goes through more [\h__\h]
and still enjoys life to the fullest
more than black people.
Nobody. It's so impressive to me. And
it's such a beautiful way to live your
life because everybody's going to go
through [\h__\h] but not everybody can
bounce back and still enjoy [\h__\h] to the
fullest. And I think it's an absolutely
incredible way to live.
This is going to seem so dramatic, but I
need you guys to take it into
consideration.
Do you have any idea
what it takes to have this country
literally built on your [\h__\h] back,
to this day still have to fight to be
treated like a decent human being, and
still have time to write a better
version of the happy birthday song?
Have you all heard it? That shit's
incredible. They got a Drake verse on
there. It's incredible. Step your [\h__\h]
up, white people. You had such a head
start.
Absolutely amazing.
At its simplest form, it just comes down
to common interest and common opinion.
The people who you have in common
interest and opinion, those are the
people you surround yourself with. Those
are your real friends. Those are your
real family. The world should not be
split into like, "Oh, white people do
this. Black people do this. If you try
to do something another culture does,
you're trying to do something that
you're not." Like, that that divides us.
That does not bring us together.
And it doesn't even need to be so cut
and dry. It goes through all aspects of
life. Comedy is like that. I'm supposed
to come up here, say some relatable [\h__\h]
that y'all probably kind of already
thought about. We make it funny. Now we
have that bond together, right? But,
there's still that judgment until we
have that bond. Like, every time I walk
on stage, every dude watching is like,
"Mhm."
Absolutely not. I ain't got nothing in
common with this dude. He got bangs.
Like, I'm not I'm not going to think
he's funny. But, as soon as I come up
here and say some relatable [\h__\h] that we
can agree on like,
"WHO IN HERE LIKE BIG TITTIES?"
All those dudes are like, "What's good,
my chance? See
See what these titties are talking
about?"
Cuz we're not that [\h__\h] different,
man. Stop dividing people just because
you're uneducated or inexperienced,
okay? That's why you're uncomfortable.
That's why you come across as so [\h__\h]
corny, and that's why you're not invited
to the cookout.
I'll bring the potato salad.
Nah, I'm just kidding. I'll I'll I'll
I'll bring chairs. It's okay.
Thank you guys so much. My name is Matt
Rife.
Thank you so much, you guys. You guys
are fantastic. Go home safe, please.